Welcome back, scum!
Kaiji returns to the silver screen!
And we give you loyal anime watchers a sneak peek!
Did he wear himself out!?
Kaiji: Masato Hagiwara
Kaiji and...
Go!
Kaiji: Tatsuya Fujiwara
Kaiji!
They face off!
Interview: Tatsuya Fujiwara x Masato Hagiwara
These two have put all their hearts into playing Kaiji!
About Kaiji himself
He's pretty much a loser. Yep, a loser.
Kaiji's a loser.
He's great at coming up with things, but that just isn't enough.
He gets out of one mess and he's right back in.
That's why I'm him in the anime and Tatsuya's him in the movie.
If you could play the Bog in real life
Nope, not happening.
Each shot is what, 4,000 yen?
Nope.
Kaiji challenges the monster machine in theaters!
Kaiji 2: Jinsei Dakkai Game, this November 5th!
打ち続けるカイジ
Kaiji keeps shooting!
この物量作戦が呼ぶ奇跡 僥倖
This is a war of materiel!
Then, a fortuitous miracle!
１段目 ２段目に続き
Not only are the first and second trays clogged, but also the third!
３段目の外れ穴の排出口の管が
詰まったのだ！
いけ！決めろ！決めちまえ
Go! Finish this!
いけー！
カイジ！
Kaiji!
His prayers were answered!
満願成就…
But in the very moment when everyone thought he'd won...
だが誰もがそう思った その瞬間！
割れる　割れる
They shatter. They shatter! They shatter!!!
割れる！
はねつけた　またしても
He was repelled! Repelled again!
はねつけた！
Spiraling Silver Spheres
何だよ 今の…
What just happened!?
はね返したぞ　縁で
Something blocked him!
何だ？なんで外れる
How'd that miss?
No way!
ウソだろ？あんなん ありかよ！
That's impossible!
外れ？
He missed?
外れって…
He missed...
セーフだったのか 今
I'm safe...
しかし どうして？
But why!?
遅くなりました
Sorry it took so long.
む… 村上
Murakami!
ええ　ここに着いたら
ピンチでしたので 指示を待たず
We saw what was happening, so we went ahead and started it up without you.
ともかく作動させました
こいつを
おおっ
See, we found it.
長く使ってませんでしたから
It's been a while, so I wasn't sure if it would work, but it seems like it was fine.
きちんと作動するかどうか
不安だったのですが
問題ないようです
電気系も大丈夫な…
The wiring looks like it's fine too.
貸せ！
あっ…
Give me that.
よし！
Excellent.
やった！これで生き残れる
All right! I'm gonna survive this!
もう何発 来ようと何の問題もない
It doesn't matter how many balls you shoot!
I'll block every single one.
すべて はね返せる
Around that hole is a ring of tiny jet nozzles.
穴の周りに
びっしりと敷き詰められた
極小の噴出口
そこから噴射される強風
This barrier of wind will block everything shot at it!
この風のバリアで
カイジ　どういうことだ？
Kaiji! What's happening!?
分かんねえ
分かんねえが大丈夫だ
I don't know!
I don't know, but it doesn't matter!
玉はクルーンにあふれている
The tray is full of balls!
まだまだ３段目には送れる
And more are coming!
送れるんだ
They're coming!
問題ねえ！吹き飛ばせる
It doesn't matter! I'll blow by that bad luck!
不運なアクシデントは！
カイジ…
Kaiji...
Look, there's so many!
量で…
量による必然で
There's so many that I have to!
Kaiji... Really!?
カイジ　そうか？
本当に そういうことなのか？
そうさ　打ち破ったんだ
Yeah!
I've smashed through!
奴らの手は すべて
Through every trick they have!
すべてな！
し… しかし カイジ
Come on, Kaiji!
あってたまるか！
They don't have anything left!
奴らに手など！
もしあるなら もっと
さっさと出したはずだ
If they did, they would have already used it!
They wouldn't hold back this long, would they!?
ここまで追い詰められてから
出すことない　だろ？
そ… そりゃそうだが
I guess...
でも…
But...
そのとおりだ
まったく そのとおり
You're right. You're exactly right.
正論さ
しかし あるんだよな
But sometimes the unexpected happens and things don't go as planned.
不測の事態
意味不明な展開ってやつが
人間の願い
Human hopes... Prayers...
願望
Ambitions... All these emotions...
期待　そういった感情は
時に誤らせる
Sometimes, they lead our minds astray!
Only now does he understand what's happening!
認識を！
今 真に何が起こっているかを！
何だ？
What?
何だよ これ！
What's happening!?
これは…
This is—
悪夢
A nightmare!
It's like a ghost dance!
まるで亡霊のダンス
浮遊し 乱舞するだけ
They waver like spirits!
命なき銀の玉
The silver balls on which he staked his life do not strike their target!
届かない！
次々に銀の玉が
当たりに向かいはするが
Even though they approach, they get no further!
それまで！
当たりには至らない
They do not strike!
結局 ただクルーン内を
徘徊するだけ
They only circle in the tray!
カイジ！
Kaiji!
バ… バカな
No way!
何だよ これ
What's going on!?
何だ この音？
What's this noise!?
吹き上げてやがんのか
They're being blown away! It's like...
ひょっとして あの周りから
風が！
It's like there's a wind blowing from the hole!
That motherfucker!
あの野郎！
何てことを！
This sucks!
入るわけがねえ
I'm never going to get one in!
こんなことされたら もう…
If this keeps up...
いくら打っても
No matter how many I shoot...
きたー！
うおっ
Here we go!
あっ！いくか？上からなら…
That works!
If I come from above...
入れ！
I can make it in!
ぐっ… ちくしょう！
Son of a—
よせ！バカ野郎！
Wait!
You moron!
たたいて詰まりが直ったら
それこそ目がなくなる！
If you hit it, it'll unclog, and then we're really fucked!
落ち着け　落ち着け カイジ
Calm down! Calm down, Kaiji!
You just need a little bit more to get it in from above!
それに もう少しだったじゃねえか
入るかもしれねえ　上からならな
そうだ そうだ！
ヤケになるな
That's it!
Stay chill!
もう少しだぞ！
あり得るって 大当たり
Just keep going!
That jackpot is yours!
いけるぞ！
いける いける いける！
You can do it!
You can do it, Kaiji!
いけるって カイジ！
カイジ！
Kaiji!
カイジ！カイジ！
Kaiji! Kaiji!
カイジ！カイジ！カイジ！
カイジさん！
カイジ君！
Kaiji!
カイジ！カイジ！カイジ！
Kaiji! Kaiji!
Yeah. I can't give up now.
そうだ　諦めるな
I've gotta fight to the end!
最後の最後まで
諦めるな！
入るかもしれねえ
I don't know if I'll make it, but I can't lose!
ねえわけじゃねえ
あの きたねえ風を打ち破っての
大当たり
If I can push through that wind, I hit the jackpot!
事実 今いきそうだった
I think I can do it!
そう　異常事態なんだ
Yeah!
Look at all those balls! He's just as bad off as I am!
３段目に玉があふれてる
こんな状態は 敵にとっても
いくぜ！
Let's go!
いくぜ いくぜ！
Let's do this!
ねじ込む！
何があっても諦めねえ！
I'm all in!
だから頼むぜ みんな！後押しを！
Back me up, guys!
うおー！
任しとけ！
Sure thing!
こうなりゃ最後まで
いくしかねえだろ！
There's no giving up now!
Yeah!
そうだ！入れろ！
入れろ！入れろ！入れろ！
Do it!
Get it in! Get it in!
入れるさ！
One of these balls is going in!
入れなきゃ 死んだも同然
If it doesn't, I'm as good as dead!
家畜だ
I'll be nothing more than livestock!
クッ… 許さない
I won't let you pull this off! I can't afford to!
許すものか
Go in! Go in!
入れ… 入れ
Go in!
入れー！
Kaiji pleads!
懇願！
Pleads as hard as he can!
圧倒的 懇願
願うは 奇跡！
He prays for a miracle!
この土壇場での奇跡
A miracle at the last moment!
生還！
Survival!
しかし…
But!
しかし起きない！
But it doesn't happen!
なかなか あのジャンプが
The jump he prays for...
起きない！
Does not happen!
起きずに消える
The balls fall without jumping!
The balls do nothing but fall!
ただ玉のみ消えていく
No!
嫌だ！
うう… 死ぬ！死んじまう
I... I'm gonna die!
もう地下は嫌だ
I don't wanna go back in the hole!
助けてくれ　誰か…
Save me! Someone save me!
助け…
あっ マズい　終わっちまう
No! It's almost over!
The balls! These balls are my life, and they're—
玉が… 命の玉が！
どうした？どうした みんな！
What's wrong with you guys!?
声がねえぞ 声が！
Can't you say anything!?
Back off! What the hell are you trying to do!?
よせ！何をする やめろ！
早く打て
Hurry up and shoot!
Once those balls are gone, you're ours.
それが終わったら確保する
カイジ！カイジ カイジ…
Kaiji!
Kaiji! Kaiji!
ふざけるな てめえ！
Back the fuck off! He's gonna sink one!
入れろよ　入れまくれ！
Sink one! Kaiji!
調べはついている
We already know your money is loaned from Teiai too.
この男も大金を
我が帝愛グループから借り受けて
このバカな勝負につぎ込んでいる
当然 今ここで大当たりが
出なければ 返す当てはない
If he doesn't hit the jackpot, there's no way you can pay it back.
となれば確保だ　この男も
So we're taking you too.
カイジ！出せよ
命に代えても出せ！
Kaiji! Do it! Do it even if it kills you!
ふざけるな！カイジ…
Come on! Kaiji! Kaiji!
２人 ともに招待しよう
We'd like to extend an invitation to both of you.
天国へ
An invitation to heaven.
カイジ！出せ　出しやがれ
Kaiji!
Hit it! Hit the jackpot!
カイジ！
Kaiji!
出せって言われても…
Man, you can say that all you want,
わずかな玉で あの風…
but with so few balls against that wind...
どうする？
What do I do?
どうしたらいい？
What can I do?
What can I do!?
どうしたら…
オラ！さっさとしろ！
何をグズグズ…
Hurry up and shoot! Stop fucking around!
うるせえ！一服ぐらいさせろ
I've been going full-speed all day! Lemme have a smoke!
こちとらタバコも吸わずに
打ち続けてきたんだ
Quit making excuses!
ガタガタ言うな！
考えろ　何かないか
Think!
Is there anything?
この苦境からの脱出
Any way out of this mess?
打破　突破
Break it down?
Break through it?
Some way to turn things around!?
起死回生の逆転！
A plan... I need a plan!
策は… 策はないか！
But there's nothing!
ない！そんなもの どう考えても
I can't think of anything!
ない！
どうした！済んだろ もうタバコは
What's wrong? Haven't you finished smoking yet?
How long are you gonna stare off into space? Hurry up and shoot!
いつまでボーッとしている？
打て！さっさと
一条
あ？
Ichijou...
提案がある
は？
Let's make...
提案だ
Let's make a deal.
このまま俺が打てば 決定する
If I keep shooting, one of two things is gonna happen.
One of us is gonna lose, and one of us is gonna win.
どちらかの勝敗が　俺かお前
You or me.
無論… 認める
One way or the other.
I... I know your odds are better.
この時点での
お前の有利は認めるが
しかし！100パーセントじゃねえ
But they're not a lock. Neither of us knows what's gonna happen.
勝負は何が起こるか分からねえ
そうだろ？
は？
Right?
だから…
So c'mon.
はあ？
何 グズグズ言ってんだ お前！
What's your problem?
訳 分かんねえ
ハッキリ言え ハッキリ！
I don't even get what you're going on about. Spit it out!
引き分け…
A draw.
引き分けで手を打たないか？
Let's call it a draw.
Buy me out!
つまり 買ってくれ
今ある残り玉を １玉400万
Buy each of the balls I have left for four mil.
30玉ほどあるから 約１億2000万
There's thirty, so that's 120 mil.
これだけあれば
俺と遠藤さんの急場はしのげる
That's enough to cover Endoh and me.
ぐっ… カイジ！
お前 何言ってんだ！
What are you saying, Kaiji!?
無論 借金は残るが
I'll still be a little bit in the hole, but I can pay that off!
まあ それはそれとして…
もういい！
Hey!
一条…
Ichijou!
アホか！
Are you nuts!?
Ichijou...
一条…
ざけんな ざけんな ざけんな！
Gimme a fuckin' break!
なーにが引き分けだ
You call this a draw? You've lost!
負けるんだよ お前は
明白じゃねえか もう！
Even a moron could see that!
ジャンプが…
バカ！何がジャンプだ
But what if they jump?
You retard! What do you mean "jump"!?
起こるか　あんなこと そうそう
There's no way in hell they'd fly like that!
跳ぶもんか　もう！
Jeez!
いいのか…
あ？
So...
打って…
So should I shoot?
いいも悪いも
I don't give a shit! Just hurry up!
さっさとやれ！
Finish up and get out of here!
燃え尽きろ！
さっさと打って 消えろ！
消えちまえ　地下行きだ 地下！
Back in the goddamn hole!
Underground, underground, underground!
地下 地下 地下！
後悔するぞ
You're gonna regret this, Ichijou!
一条…
Really? Seriously?
バーカ！
何を言っとるんだ お前は
もういい！
御託はもういいから打て！
I've had enough shooting the shit! Just plain shoot!
今打て！すぐ打て！さあ打て！
Shoot now! Right now! Go ahead and shoot!
カイジ！頼む！何とかしろ
Please! Kaiji!
Do something! Anything! Kaiji!
い… 今 何とかしやがれ
カイジ！
Thirty balls left...
残り30玉
みんな 力をくれ
Everyone! Lend me your strength!
俺に 奇跡を…
Give me a miracle!
奇跡を与えてくれ！
Grant me that miracle!
頼む！
カイジさん！
Please!
Kaiji!
カイジ！
入れる！諦めるもんか！
Sink it!
I can't give up! Not until the end!
最後の最後まで
入れる　入れる　入れる！
I'm gonna hit the jackpot.
I'll sink a ball!
Right in that hole!
入れてやる！
見せる　見せてやる！
I'll show you! I'll show you all!
俺の勝負強さを！
I'll show you that I can win!
チッ 救えねえ　バカ丸出し
Wow, he's hopeless.
You can't do a thing.
どうにもなるかよ
あの風のカーテンがある限り
Not as long as I have this curtain of wind!
見ろ！
Go!
いけー！
バカめ　同じだ
Idiot.
Nothing will change, no matter how many balls you shoot!
何玉 来ようと
ムダな熱狂
His spirit, his cries, all in vain!
ムダな咆哮
ムダな血
His blood shed in vain!
It flows forth!
流血
玉
The balls!
The money!
金
命！
His very life!
Jump!
ジャンプ… ジャンプ！
There!
きた！
Th...ere...
もっと高く… 高く
Higher!
Just a bit higher!
もっともっと… 高く跳べ！
Soar higher!
そして 後悔せしめよ！
And...
Ichijou! You will regret this!
一条を！
カイジ！
Kaiji!
一条…
Ichijou! Ichijou! Ichijou!
一条… 一条
一条　一条　一条　一条
Ichijou! Ichijou! Ichijou! Ichijou!
一条！一条！一条！一条…
Ichijou!
It's over!
終わり 終わり！終戦
You're finished! Out of balls!
玉切れ　敗者決定！
You lose!
地獄
Down! Down to hell with you!
地獄行き！
ウソだ…
Impossible...
夢だろ これ
I'm just dreaming.
夢に決まってる
This has to be a nightmare.
ところがどっこい
夢じゃありません
No, no it isn't.
It's reality.
現実です
これが現実
This is reality.
Reality!
現実です！
さあ！
Now!
If you'll kindly peel that loser off the platform and into the abyss!
台から引っぺがし
地獄へ連れてってください
敗者を！
絶たれた希望
Kaiji's hopes, cruelly shattered!
無残！カイジ！
生き延びる道は もう尽きたか
Are all his avenues for survival blocked off?
Kaiji! Kaiji! Kaiji!!!
カイジ　カイジ　カイジ！
Proverbs of Kaiji Returns!
Prayers... Ambitions... All these emotions... Sometimes, they lead our minds astray!
Only now does he understand what's happening!
This is Kaiji S2 DVD-box 1!
It goes on sale September 21st!
Look at the fabulous extras!
And on the 24th, we're holding an event to celebrate its release!
For more info, visit our homepage!